{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "IRON MAN: What song plays at the beginning of the movie?",
      "choices": [
        "Iron Man by Black Sabbath",
        "Back in Black by AC/DC",
        "Ordinary World by Duran Duran",
        "Stairway to Heaven by Led Zeppelin"
      ],
      "answer": "Back in Black by AC/DC"
    },
    {
      "question": "THE INCREDIBLE HULK: What does Tony tell Thaddeus Ross at the end of the film?",
      "choices": [
        "That he wants to study The Hulk",
        "That he knows about S.H.I.E.L.D",
        "That they're putting team together",
        "That Thaddeus owes him money"
      ],
      "answer": "That they're putting team together"
    },
    {
      "question": "IRON MAN 2: What fake name does Natasha use when she first meets Tony?",
      "choices": [
        "Natalie Rushman",
        "Natalia Romanoff",
        "Nicole Rohan",
        "Naya Rabe"
      ],
      "answer": "Natalie Rushman"
    },
    {
      "question": "THOR: What does Thor want <another> of when he's in the diner?",
      "choices": [
        "A slice of pie",
        "A piece of toast",
        "A cup of coffee",
        "Coca-Cola"
      ],
      "answer": "A cup of coffee"
    },
    {
      "question": "CAPTAIN AMERICA: THE FIRST AVENGER: Where does Peggy tell Steve she wants to meet him for a dance, before he plunges into the ice?",
      "choices": [
        "The Cotton club",
        "The Stork Club",
        "El Morocco",
        "The Copacabana"
      ],
      "answer": "The Stork Club"
    },
    {
      "question": "AVENGERS: AGE OF ULTRON: What word does Tony utter that makes Steve say, <Language>?",
      "choices": ["Crap!", "Asshole!", "Shit!", "Idiot!"],
      "answer": "Shit!"
    },
    {
      "question": "THOR: THE DARK WORLD: Where do Sif and Volstagg hide the Reality Stone at the end of the movie?",
      "choices": [
        "On Vormir",
        "In a vault on Asgard",
        "Inside Sif'sword",
        "The gave it to the collector"
      ],
      "answer": "The gave it to the collector"
    },
    {
      "question": "CAPTAIN AMERICA: CIVIL WAR: Who ISN'T on Iron Man's team?",
      "choices": ["Vision", "Black Panter", "Hawkeye", "Black Widow"],
      "answer": "Hawkeye"
    },
    {
      "question": "DOCTOR STRANGE: What type of doctor is Stephen Strange?",
      "choices": [
        "Neurosurgeon",
        "Trauma Surgeon",
        "Plastic Surgeon",
        "Cardiothoracic Surgeon"
      ],
      "answer": "Neurosurgeon"
    },
    {
      "question": "GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY VOL. 2: Finish this line: I'm _______, y'all!",
      "choices": ["Superman", "Underlog", "Peter Pan", "Mary Poppins"],
      "answer": "Mary Poppins"
    }
  ]
}
